https://idrahaje.org/cms/about-us/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Camp Id-Ra-Ha-Je (“Camp” or “We”) and www.idrahaje.org (“Website”).  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by Camp and this Website.  It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through Camp and the Website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
How policy changes will be communicated.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owner of the information collected by Camp and the Website.  We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
Credit card information is collected by Cashlinq, WePay, Stripe, and Bambora as our outside processors.  If credit card information is sent to us in paper or other non-electronic format, it is entered into one of those two processors online and shredded.
For safety and security purposes, the operation of Camp, and to provide health care and other benefits to Camp employees pursuant to Colorado State Law, personally identifiable information is collected by Camp regarding summer staff, full-time staff, and all summer campers, including without limitation name, address, government identification, application materials, health and other records, reports, and related information.  This information is not shared with outside organizations unless Camp is required to by law.
Camp has the following Document Retention Policy related to records it collects from you:
5 years
Camper’s medical history
7 years
Bank statements
Credit card statements
Checks (paid and cancelled)
Employee agreements
Employee applications
Contracts
Pay Checks
Personnel files
Salary and wage changes
Payroll 941 forms
W-2 Forms
Records to be retained until Camper reaches age 23
Campers’ files
We will use your information to respond to you should you contact us, and for Camp security and general operations.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill a request from you or to otherwise comply with the law.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via text message, e-mail, or regular mail in the future to tell you about Camp related information, opportunities, and activities, as well as changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  Laptops, tablet, phones, or other devices are connected to the Camp server through a virtual personal network (VPN) and the server is encrypted and password protected.
Changes to this Policy
We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time.  You may check back on this page at any time to see our current policy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 303-838-5668 or via email at info@idrahaje.org
© 2020 Camp Id-Ra-Ha-Je
